<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">My Random Pony</string>
    <string name="settings_internet_warn">Enabled, but your network connection is unavailable</string>
    <string name="settings_load_error">Your network connection is unavailable or \"WiFi only\" mode is enabled</string>
    <string name="settings_progress_msg">Wait…</string>
    <string name="settings_progress_title">Downloading</string>
    <string name="settings_enable">Enabled</string>
    <string name="settings_next_image">Next</string>
    <string name="settings_only_mobile">Mobile screen resolution only</string>
    <string name="settings_radio_1">once a day</string>
    <string name="settings_radio_2">once a week</string>
    <string name="settings_radio_3">once a month</string>
    <string name="settings_preview">Preview</string>
    <string name="settings_preview_setbackground">Background has been changed</string>
    <string name="ok">OK</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="settings_update_error">mylittlewallpaper.com: cannot be reached</string>
    <string name="settings_download_error">Downloading error</string>
    <string name="settings_cancel_image">Cancel</string>
    <string name="settings_edit_image">Edit</string>
    <string name="settings_image_cancel1">No edited image</string>
    <string name="settings_image_cancel2">Cancel: unknown error</string>
    <string name="settings_image_edit">Editing</string>
    <string name="settings_wifi_only">WiFi only</string>
    <string name="hint_edit_first_click">No image. To download, click \"Next\"</string>
    <string name="hint_first_edit_text">After editing, click on the resulting image again to set it as the background.\n\nReturn to the original image - press \"Cancel\".</string>
    <string name="hint_first_next_alert_msg">If you like the image, click on it to set it as the background!\n\nTo resize or crop, press \"Edit\", return to the original image - press \"Cancel\".</string>
    <string name="hint_first_launch_alert_title">Hi!</string>
    <string name="hint_first_launch_alert_msg">You can set a new background right now by clicking on the \"Next\" button, or check the box \"Enabled\" and wait for a new day!\n\nIf you have any questions, look in the \"Help\"!</string>
    <string name="activity_help_title">Help</string>
    <string name="help_text">
        <![CDATA[
        When you first launch the application, you must enable it by clicking on the <b>\"Enabled\"</b> button, and the application will start working in the background. That\'s it!<br/>
        You can also choose the frequency of changing the wallpaper and choose whether it is necessary to change the wallpaper only when connected to a WiFi network.<br/>
        If you are impatient and you want to change the wallpaper right now, click on the <b>\"Next\"</b> button, wait for the image to load, and then click on it to set it as a background!<br/><br/>

        Checkboxes:<br/>
        - <b>Enabled</b>: enabling / disabling the wallpaper change<br/>
        - <b>Mobile screen resolution only</b>: search for images with mobile screen resolution only<br/>
        - <b>WiFi only</b>: download new wallpapers only via WiFi (does not apply to the <b>\"Next\"</b> button)<br/><br/>

        Radio buttons allow you to choose the frequency of changing the wallpaper:<br/>
        - <b>Once a day</b>: the wallpaper will change shortly after 00:00 of the next day<br/>
        - <b>Once a week</b>: the wallpaper will change shortly after 00:00 on Sunday or Monday (it depends on your system settings) of the next week<br/>
        - <b>Once a month</b>: the wallpaper will change shortly after 00:00 on the 1st of the next month<br/><br/>

        Buttons:<br/>
        - <b>Cancel</b>: resetting all changes after the <b>\"Edit\"</b> button. After that, you need to click on the image to set it as the background<br/>
        - <b>Edit</b>: allows you to crop the image if it is too large. After editing the image, you need to click it again to set it as the background<br/>
        - <b>Next</b>: download a new image right now. To set new image as a background just click on it<br/><br/>

        <b>Image</b>: wallpaper preview. Click on it to set it as the background!<br/><br/>

        <b>Link under the image</b>: after successfully downloading the image, a link will appear under it leading to page on http://mylittlewallpaper.com, where you can download this image<br/><br/>

        You can also change the theme of the application! Themes available in \3-dot\ menu.<br/><br/>

        <i>Notice for Android 8 users and higher</i>: due to the new system policy, starting from Android 8 and higher, for the correct operation of this app, constant display of notification is required.<br/>
        So you can\'t disable the notification without disabling the wallpaper change.
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="menu_item_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_item_about">About</string>
    <string name="about_text">
        My Little Pony © Hasbro\n\n

        All images are located on mylittlewallpaper.com and belong to their authors.\n\n

        \"My Random Pony\" app is developed by Evgeniy Doctor. All rights reserved. ©\n
        The app was released on November 24, 2016.\n
        This is a third-party mobile app for accessing the images on http://mylittlewallpaper.com. The developer is not responsible for the content of the images.\n\n

        Open source: https://github.com/EvgeniyDoctor/MyRandomPony\n\n

        Also listen to my music and mixes! https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCvPZd3PqeTxNciigUdmgRaQ\n\n

        Support me:\n
        - by buying my music: https://arklysis.bandcamp.com\n
        - by money transfer: https://paypal.me/evgeniydoctor
    </string>
    <string name="changing_wallpaper_progress_title">Changing</string>
    <string name="open_image_on_site">Open this image on the site</string>
    <string name="activity_about_title">About</string>
    <string name="activity_themes_title">Themes</string>
    <string name="theme_apply">Apply</string>
</resources>
